<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News And Updates Archives - Sports Updates 24</title>
	<atom:link href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/category/news-and-updates/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://poc.groupdesk.io/category/news-and-updates/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:55:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Which teams have qualified for UEFA Champions League group stage for the 2023/24 season?</title>
		<link>http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-2023-24-season/</link>
					<comments>http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-2023-24-season/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News And Updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://poc.groupdesk.io/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 2022/23 Champions League hasn’t even reached its climax yet but we already have a fairly clear picture about which clubs will be in the group stages of the 2023/24 Champions League.The European club season has almost come to an end and, if we’re being brutally honest, it’s been a bit of a let-down in&#8230; <a class="more-link" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-2023-24-season/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Which teams have qualified for UEFA Champions League group stage for the 2023/24 season?</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-2023-24-season/">Which teams have qualified for UEFA Champions League group stage for the 2023/24 season?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io">Sports Updates 24</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><br />The 2022/23 Champions League hasn’t even reached its climax yet but we already have a fairly clear picture about which clubs will be in the group stages of the 2023/24 Champions League.The European club season has almost come to an end and, if we’re being brutally honest, it’s been a bit of a let-down in terms of title races in the so-called ‘top’ leagues, hasn’t it? Barcelona and Napoli had LaLiga and Serie A respectively wrapped up months ago, Manchester City winning the Premier League felt inevitable as soon as Arsenal slipped up once and, for all their considerable issues, Paris Saint-Germain never really looked like surrendering their lead in Ligue 1. Thank goodness for the Bundesliga.European winners still to be decidedOf course, the identity of this season’s Champions League winners is still unknown, although City are overwhelming favourites to see off Inter to win the trophy for the first time in their history. Sevilla would be guaranteed to win a seventh Europa League were they not up against European final specialist José Mourinho and Roma in the final, while we mustn’t forget about the Europa Conference League final, which will see West Ham take on Fiorentina.But we will forget about the Europa Conference League for now, as, unlike the Champions League and Europa League finals, it will have no bearing on which teams will feature in the 2023/24 Champions League, which will be the last edition of the competition until a new format is introduced in 2024/25.Which of the 32 spots are still to be decided?You know the drill. 32 teams will take part in the group stages, with 25 spots already taken. The winners of this season’s Champions League automatically qualify for next year’s but City and Inter have already qualified anyway. The Europa League winners, Sevilla or Roma, will take spot 26, with the six remaining teams decided by the qualifying rounds, which will take place from June to August.2023/24 Champions League group stage qualifiers by country<br />
England: Manchester City, Arsenal, Manchester United, Newcastle United<br />
Spain: Barcelona, Real Madrid, Atlético Madrid, Real Sociedad<br />
Italy: Napoli, Lazio, Inter, Milan<br />
Germany: Bayern Munich, Borussia Dortmund, RB Leipzig, Union Berlin<br />
France: Paris Saint-Germain, Lens<br />
Portugal: Benfica, Porto<br />
Netherlands: Feyenoord<br />
Ukraine: Shakhtar Donetsk<br />
Austria: FC Salzburg<br />
Scotland: Celtic<br />
2023/24 Champions League group stage qualifiers by potPot 12022/23 Champions League winners2022/23 Europa League winnersManchester City (ENG)Barcelona (ESP)Napoli (ITA)Bayern Munich (GER)Paris Saint-Germain (FRA)Benfica (POR)Pot 1 or 2Inter (ITA)Pot 1 or 3Feyenoord (NED)Pot 2Real Madrid (ESP)Manchester United (ENG)Borussia Dortmund (GER)Atlético Madrid (ESP)RB Leipzig (GER)Porto (POR)Arsenal (ENG)Pot 2 or 3Shakhtar Donetsk (UKR)Pot 3FC Salzburg (AUS)Milan (ITA)Lazio (ITA)Red Star Belgrade (SRB)Pot 3 or 4Real Sociedad (ESP)Celtic (SCO)Newcastle United (ENG)Four winners from Champions Path qualificationTwo winners from League Path qualificationPot 4Union Berlin (GER)Lens (FRA)Champions League pots explainedThe 32 teams will be divided into eight groups of four, which will be composed of one team from each of the four pots, ensuring that all groups are roughly of the same standard. Clubs from the same country cannot be drawn to play against each other in the group stage.Several teams don’t yet know which pot they are in because we don’t know the winner of this year’s Champions League or which teams will progress from qualification. The full pot list won’t be confirmed until the qualifying rounds finish in August.Notable ins and outsWhile most of the names above are the usual runners and riders, there are one or two that stand out, such as Newcastle United, who last qualified for the Champions League group stage in 2002/03, the same year French side Lens last featured. German side Union Berlin will be playing in the competition for the first time in their history after finishing fourth in the Bundesliga. Among the biggest names to have missed out are six-time winners Liverpool, who reached three finals in five years from 2018 to 2022, and Juventus, who suffered a 10-point deduction in Serie A and lost at home to Milan in the penultimate league game of the season, which ended their challenge.<br />
<br /><a href="https://en.as.com/soccer/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-202324-season-n/">Source link </a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-2023-24-season/">Which teams have qualified for UEFA Champions League group stage for the 2023/24 season?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io">Sports Updates 24</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/which-teams-have-qualified-for-uefa-champions-league-group-stage-for-the-2023-24-season/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Barcelona defender Mapi León says she “isn’t going to the World Cup” and “can’t go back” to the Spain team</title>
		<link>http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team/</link>
					<comments>http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News And Updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://poc.groupdesk.io/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FC Barcelona defender, Mapi León spoke to Catalan radio station RAC1 as part of their Tú Dirás programme, in which she opened up on whether or not the situation has changed regarding the impasse in the Spanish Women’s National Team. Last year, 15 players, the majority from FC Barcelona, wrote identical emails to Luis Rubiales,&#8230; <a class="more-link" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team/">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Barcelona defender Mapi León says she “isn’t going to the World Cup” and “can’t go back” to the Spain team</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team/">Barcelona defender Mapi León says she “isn’t going to the World Cup” and “can’t go back” to the Spain team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io">Sports Updates 24</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><br />FC Barcelona defender, Mapi León spoke to Catalan radio station RAC1 as part of their Tú Dirás programme, in which she opened up on whether or not the situation has changed regarding the impasse in the Spanish Women’s National Team. Last year, 15 players, the majority from FC Barcelona, wrote identical emails to Luis Rubiales, head of the Spanish FA (RFEF), saying that due to their “emotional state and as such [their] health”, they were unavailable for selection to the squad. The players all published a statement that did not highlight the exact reasons as to why they were unhappy with Vilda’s management, and as such this has caused more harm than good for everyone involved. Since this moment, Spain’s national team, which went into Euro 2022 as one of the favourites, has suffered huge damage on all sides. Nobody has emerged as the victor in this.Full screenJenni Hermoso and Irene Paredes have both returned to the squad ahead of the World Cup in Australia and New Zealand.INMA FLORESDiarioASIrene and Jenni have returned to Spain: will the other players?However, over the past few months, with the World Cup in Australia and New Zealand looming, jigsaw pieces have started to move and there has been a sliver of light that has crept through the gaps: both Irene Paredes and Jenni Hermoso have returned to the squad which has seen massive overhaul given the amount of players who have declared themselves as not available. Spain have three difficult tournament opponents and will ply against Costa Rica, Zambia and Japan in the group stage.With the return of Jenni and Irene, rumours have swirled that other players may also be in negotiations with the RFEF regarding a possible return to the fray. When asked whether she was likely to make a comeback, Mapi León, a firm favourite in the Barcelona fanbase, all but ruled herself out completely.Full screenSpain lost in the Euro 2022 quarter-finals to eventual champions England.MATTHEW CHILDSREUTERSMapi says she ‘deserves’ to be at the World Cup“Right now I’m not going to the World Cup”, she said, “It makes me sad, as I deserve it and I contributed to getting the team there, but it’s not a decision that you take lightly and and it’s not easy. My decision is clear. Mapi León has a way of living and she has values to stick to. I can’t go back, there has to be changes. If they tell me and there is a plan, but I don’t see changes.”Mapi León did not open up on exactly what those changes are, whether she wants the manager gone or more simple, structural changes to the setup with the National Team. This in itself is the root of the confusion from many: it is fair to ask for changes but to do so with half of the public side of the message covered is only going to create anger and suspicion. Full screenMapi León is considered one of the world&#8217;s top defenders.RODOLFO MOLINADiarioASJorge Vilda has a ‘totally committed’ squadVilda, for his part, has not yet responded to the comments, but said back in April that the players that he had selected for the friendlies against Norway and China were all “totally committed” to playing for the national side. All of the 23 players are ready to play, to perform and give their all. It’s an attractive team in terms of the style and we are creating a very cohesive group with players who are totally committed.”“If we all go in the right direction and we all try our best, playing how we want to play, which are bigger than some irrelevant things, I’m sure we will achieve all the objectives that we set ourselves”, he said.<br />
<br /><a href="https://en.as.com/soccer/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team-n/">Source link </a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team/">Barcelona defender Mapi León says she “isn’t going to the World Cup” and “can’t go back” to the Spain team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://poc.groupdesk.io">Sports Updates 24</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://poc.groupdesk.io/2023/05/29/barcelona-defender-mapi-leon-says-she-isnt-going-to-the-world-cup-and-cant-go-back-to-the-spain-team/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
